evolutiontravel.net 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy - ETN

**PRIVACY POLICY** \- Data Protection Act  
By means of this note Evolution Travel Network Ltd (hereinafter "ETN") seeks to inform visiting users of the  www.etnstore.com website (hereinafter the "Site") of the  Policy adopted with regard to the protection of personal information, emphasizing  its own commitment and attention with regard to the safeguarding of the  privacy of visitors to the Site.   
Navigating the Site is free and requires no registration, with the exception of some specific individual services or the access to reserved areas.  Accordingly, where the visitor intends to provide his/her own personal information in order to have access to such other services (i.e., a request for information, subscription to the newsletter, etc.)1, this shall be expressly notified, within the meaning of the British Data Protection Act, with an indication (by way of example) of the purpose and mode of utilisation of the information by ETN, as well as the right to request at any time cancellation of the information or the updating of same.   
INFORMATION ON THE SAFEGUARDING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Within the meaning of the British Data Protection Act (hereinafter “Data Protection Act”) ETN provides the following information.  

  1.  **The Holder and Party in Charge of Utilisation**  
The Holder of the right to utilisation, within the meaning of Section 1 of the Data Protection Act, is the company ETN with registered office in London (UK), 37 Warren Street, W1T 6AD, UK.   
**  
**
  2. **Type of personal information processed**  
To obtain access to the Reserved Area2 of the Site it is necessary to arrange for a user name and password which is provided to the ETN Staff. After logging in, the user will have the opportunity to have access to the entire section of the portal downloading the material made available. To obtain access to the other areas in the Site it is not necessary to carry out any registration.  There are, however, within the Site services for the use of which it is necessary to supply your own data: in particular your data could be requested in order to contact you, to have you subscribe to the Newsletter, etc3.

In the event ETN were to acquire information and personal data, it shall inform the users by way of prevention, within the meaning of the  Data Protection Act, as to the specific purpose for which such data are requested and in what manner they will be used.  Where necessary, ETN will provide for the acquisition of the specific consent of the user relative to the utilisation of the information (e.g. for subscription to the Newsletter).  By way of example, the personal information requested may be such as name and surnames, telephone number, email address and any other information that the user agrees to supply in order to use the services by means of the compilation of a specific registration module. ETN shall use the personal information collected online for the sole purpose indicated at the time of registration, such as, by way of example, to respond to your request or to send the Newsletter.  
In any event, no personal information shall be collected on minors.

Data related to logon and navigation within the Site (such as the address in  URI-Uniform Resource Identifier notation of the resources requested, the time of the  request, the method used in submitting the request to the server, the  size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code indicating the condition of the response given by the server (successful, error, etc.) and other parameters relative to the operating system and to the computer environment of the user) are collected and used anonymously for the sole purpose of preparing anonymous statistical information for the use of the Site and to verify its proper  operation. The data shall be cancelled once the proper time for rendering of the services illustrated in the Site has passed.

  3.  **Optional nature of the grant of personal information**  
Except for the information relative to the navigation within the Site (see Point 2), the grant of personal information by means of the compilation of the request module is of an optional nature. Failure to grant same, however, may entail an inability to have access to specific services and to obtain what is possibly being requested.   
 
  4.  **Manner of utilisation of the information in the field of communication**  
Save as may be otherwise indicated in the specific information presented within the Site, personal information shall be handled with automated tools and for the time that is strictly necessary to pursue the various purposes for which it has been collected, thereafter it shall be destroyed.   
ETN guarantees the lawful and accurate utilisation of the personal information supplied by means of the Site, in full compliance with the regulations in force, as well as the maximum confidentiality of the information supplied at the time of registration.   
The data shall not be disclosed or distributed to third parties excepts upon the limits and  terms expressly indicated in the specific information provided to the user from time to time and subject to the prior consent of this last.    
Specific security measures have been implemented in order to prevent the loss of information or its illicit or incorrect use, or the unauthorised access thereto.  All information collected shall be transmitted by means of a secure connexion so as to prevent interception by unknown parties.1  
 
  5.  **"Profiling" tools2**  
ETN shall not carry out any promotional and/or advertising communication without the prior and express consent of the user.   
No profiling tools of the user are used in this Site (e.g. cookies, spyware).  
 
  6.  **Links to other sites**  
This informational material is provided only for the Site http://www.www.etnstore.com and not for any other web sites that may be possibly linked and consulted by the user by means of a connecting link.  
ETN shall not be held responsible for any personal information supplied by users to external subjects or to possible web sites linked to this Site.  
 
  7.  **Rights of the interested parties**  
Within the meaning of Section 7 of the Data Protection Act you have the right to obtain information about the use of your data, including, among others, 1) obtaining, without delay,  confirmation of the existence or not of the personal information concerned [...]; 2) obtaining: a) an indication of the source of the personal information, the purpose and manner of  utilisation, the logical reason for the utilisation carried out with the help of electronic instruments,  the identifying data of the holder or responsible party, the subjects or category of subjects to whom such data may be communicated or who might become aware in their capacity as parties responsible or in charge; the updating, correcting or rather, in the event you are interested, the integration of the information; b) the cancellation,  transformation to an anonymous form or blocking of information handled in violation of the law; 3) the opposition, in whole or in part, to the utilisation of the personal information concerned, contemplated for the purposes of business information or for sending advertising or direct sale material or rather to carry out market research or business communications.  

You may exercise these rights at any time by writing to the email address: privacy@etnstore.com

 The full text of the Data Protection Act may be consulted on the Site of the Information Commissioner’s Office - http://www.ico.gov.uk/.
